Guide to the Language Resource Center collection, circa 1963-1983.
Language Resource Center collection,
- Reel-to-reel tape recordings
  - LCTL published
    - Cantonese Speak Cantonese Book II, Undated; TR-13938 (Box 44)
      LRC #: CTA 7
    - Cantonese Speak Cantonese Book II, Undated; TR-13939; Moldy (Box 44)
      LRC #: CTA 8
    - Cantonese Speak Cantonese Book II, Undated; TR-13940 (Box 44)
      LRC #: CTA 9
    - Toishan Cantonese DLI Test, Undated; TR-13941 (Box 45)
      LRC #: TOI
    - Cantonese Beginning Chinese Reader, Undated; TR-13942; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 20
    - Cantonese Beginning Chinese Reader, Undated; TR-13943; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 21
    - Cantonese Beginning Chinese Reader, Undated; TR-13944; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 22
    - Cantonese Beginning Chinese Reader, Undated; TR-13945; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 23
    - Cantonese Beginning Chinese Reader, Undated; TR-13946; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 24
    - Cantonese Beginning Chinese Reader, Undated; TR-13947; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 25
    - Cantonese Beginning Chinese Reader, Undated; TR-13948; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 26
    - Chinese 112, Undated; TR-13949; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 27
    - Chinese 112, Undated; TR-13950; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 28
    - Chinese: Cantonese, Undated; TR-13951; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 29
    - Chinese: Cantonese, Undated; TR-13952; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 30
    - Chinese: Cantonese, Undated; TR-13953; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 31
    - Chinese: Cantonese, Undated; TR-13954; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 32
    - Chinese: Cantonese, Undated; TR-13955; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 33
    - Chinese: Cantonese, Undated; TR-13956; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 34
    - Chinese: Cantonese, Undated; TR-13957; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 35
    - Chinese: Cantonese, Undated; TR-13958; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 36
    - Chinese: Cantonese, Undated; TR-13959; Yale University Press (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTD 37
    - Cantonese Basic Course Master Lesson 6, Undated; TR-13960 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Basic Course Master Lesson 7, Undated; TR-13961 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Basic Course Master Lesson 8, Undated; TR-13962 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Basic Course Master Lesson 9, Undated; TR-13963 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Basic Course Master Lesson 10, Undated; TR-13964 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Basic Course Master Lesson 11, Undated; TR-13965 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Basic Course Master Lesson 12, Undated; TR-13966 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Basic Course Master Lesson 13, Undated; TR-13967 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Basic Course Master Lesson 14, Undated; TR-13968 (Box 54)
    - Speak Cantonese Book 1 Lessons 1 - 5 (student copy #1), Undated; TR-13969 (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTA
    - Speak Cantonese Book 1 Lessons 1 - 5 (student copy #2), Undated; TR-13970 (Box 54)
    - Speak Cantonese Book 1 Lessons 1 - 5 (student copy), Undated; TR-13971 (Box 54)
    - Speak Cantonese Book I Lesson 24 (student copy), Undated; TR-13972 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations conv 1,2,3 (student copy #4), Undated; TR-13973; Moldy (Box 54)
      LRC #: CTS
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations conv 1,2,3 (student copy #6), Undated; TR-13974 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations conv 4,5,6 (student copy #2), Undated; TR-13975 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations conv 4,5,6 (student copy #3), Undated; TR-13976 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations conv 4,5,6 (student copy #5), Undated; TR-13977 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations conv 4,5,6 (student copy #7), Undated; TR-13978 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations conv 4,5,6 (student copy #8), Undated; TR-13979 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations conv 7,8,9 (student copy #3), Undated; TR-13980 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations conv 7,8,9 (student copy #4), Undated; TR-13981 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations conv 7,8,9 (student copy #5), Undated; TR-13982 (Box 54)
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations conv 10-12 (student copy #1), Undated; TR-13983 (Box 54)
  - Non-Cornell teacher's material
    - Turkish World Foreign Language Records, Undated; TR-13984 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKW 2
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13985 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 23
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13986 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 24
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13987 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 25
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13988 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 26
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13989 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 27
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13990 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 28
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13991 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 29
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13992 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 30
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13993 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 31
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13994 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 32
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13995 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 33
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13996 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 34
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13997 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 35
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13998 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 36
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-13999 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 37
    - Turkish Grammer, Undated; TR-14000 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TKG 38
    - Taiwanese Amoy - Bodruau Wu Revision, Undated; TR-14001 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TS 1
    - Taiwanese, Undated; TR-14002 (Box 5)
    - Taiwanese Amoy - Bodruau Wu Revision, Undated; TR-14003 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TS 2
    - Taiwanese, Undated; TR-14004 (Box 5)
    - Taiwanese Amoy - Bodruau Wu Revision, Undated; TR-14005 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TS 3
    - Taiwanese, Undated; TR-14006 (Box 5)
    - Taiwanese Amoy - Bodruau Wu Revision, Undated; TR-14007 (Box 5)
      LRC #: TS 4
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14008 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 100-101
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14009 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 102-103
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14010 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 104-105
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14011 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 106-107
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14012 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 108-109
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14013 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 110-111
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14014 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 112-113
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14015 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 114-115
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14016 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 116-117
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14017 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 118-119
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14018 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 120-121
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14019 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 122-123
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14020 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 124-125
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14021 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 126-127
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14022 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 128-129
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14023 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 130-131
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14024 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 132-133
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14025 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 134-135
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14026 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 136-137
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14027 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 138-139
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14028 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 140-141
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14029 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 142-143
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14030 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 144-145
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14031 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 78
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14032 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 79
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14033 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 80
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14034 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 81
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14035 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 82
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14036 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 83
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14037 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 84
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14038 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 85
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14039 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 86
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14040 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 87
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14041 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 88
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14042 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 89
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14043 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 90
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14044 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 91
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14045 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 92
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14046 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 93
    - Ping Shu Storytelling, Peking Drum Singing, Poetry, etc, Undated; TR-14047 (Box 12)
      LRC #: TAI 94
    - Language and the Brain Tutorial, 1972; TR-14048; Linguistic Society of America (Box 63)
      Duplicated from cassette
      LRC #: LAB 2
    - Language and the Brain Tutorial, 1972; TR-14049; Linguistic Society of America (Box 63)
      LRC #: LAB 3
    - Primer of Newspaper Chinese, Undated; TR-14050 (Box 23)
      LRC #: CTN 1
    - Primer of Newspaper Chinese, Undated; TR-14051 (Box 23)
      LRC #: CTN 2
    - Primer of Newspaper Chinese, Undated; TR-14052 (Box 23)
      LRC #: CTN 3
    - Primer of Newspaper Chinese, Undated; TR-14053 (Box 23)
      LRC #: CTN 4
    - Cantonese Practice, Undated; TR-14054 (Box 23)
      LRC #: CTP 1
    - Cantonese Exam Story, Undated; TR-14055 (Box 23)
      LRC #: CTQ
  - Standard published
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14056; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      Content: ante todo
      LRC #: SPP 0
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14057; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      Content: chapter 1 part 1 (numbers for all)
      LRC #: SPP 1.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14058; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      Duplicate.
      LRC #: SPP 1.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14059; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 10.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14060; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 10.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14061; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 11.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14062; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 11.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14063; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 12.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14064; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 12.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14065; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 13.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14066; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 13.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14067; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 14.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14068; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 14.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14069; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 15.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14070; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 15.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14071; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 16.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14072; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 16.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14073; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 17.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14074; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 18.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14075; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 18.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14076; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 19.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14077; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 19.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14078; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 2.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14079; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 2.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14080; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 20
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14081; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 3.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14082; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 3.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14083; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 4.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14084; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 4.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14085; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 5.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14086; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 5.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14087; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 6.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14088; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 6.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14089; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 7.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14090; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 7.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14091; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 8.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14092; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 8.2
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14093; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 9.1
    - Puntos de Partida, 1983-05; TR-14094; Knorre, Dorwick et al.; Random House; 3.75 speed, track a, head tail foil (Box 1)
      LRC #: SPP 9.2
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1975-08-27; TR-14095; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, HALF TRACK, MONO, ONE SIDE, DUBBING MASTER, EDITED, AUTO FOILED. (Box 1)
      CONTENT: 31AB, 32AB
      LRC #: SS 1
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1977-06-13; TR-14096; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, MONO, DUPLICATE, HALF TRACK, FOILED HEAD TAIL. (Box 1)
      CONTENTS: 46AB, 47AB, 48AB, 49AB
      LRC #: SS 10
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1977-06-13; TR-14097; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, MONO, DUPLICATE, HALF TRACK. (Box 1)
      CONTENTS; 1ABC, 2A, 3A, 4AB, 8B
      LRC #: SS 11
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1977-06-13; TR-14098; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, MONO, HALF TRACK, DUPLICATE, FOILED HEAD TAIL. (Box 1)
      CONTENTS; 5AB, 6ABC, 7ABC
      LRC #: SS 12
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1976-03-12; TR-14099; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, TRACK A, HEAD TAIL FOIL, DUPLICATE, (Box 1)
      CONTENTS:132A, 133A, 134AB, CHAP 3 DIALOGUE
      LRC #: SS 13
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1977-06-13; TR-14100; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, MONO, DUPLICATE, HALF TRACK, HEAD TAIL FOILED, (Box 1)
      CONTENTS: 136ABC, 137ABC, 138A
      LRC #: SS 14
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1977-06-13; TR-14101; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, MONO, MASTER, HALF TRACK. (Box 1)
      CONTENTS: 95AB, 101AB, 102A, 103A, 104ABC
      LRC #: SS 15
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1977-06-13; TR-14102; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, mono, master recording, half track., foiled head toe (Box 1)
      Contents:96ABC, 97ABCD, 98A
      LRC #: SS 16
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1975-08-27; TR-14103; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, HALF TRACK, MONO, DUBBING MASTER, EDITED, AUTO FOILED, ONE SIDE. (Box 1)
      CONTENT: 35AB, 36AB
      LRC #: SS 2
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1977-06-13; TR-14104; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, HALF TRACK, MONO, ONE SIDE, DUBBING MASTER, EDITED, AUTO FOILED. (Box 1)
      CONTENT: 89AC, 90AB, 92A
      LRC #: SS 3
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1975-08-27; TR-14105; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 ips, mono, half track, one side, dubbing master, edited, foiled auto. (Box 1)
      Content: 37ab
      LRC #: SS 4
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1975-09-09; TR-14106; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, MONO, HALF TRACK, ONE SIDE, DUBBING MASTER, EDITED, AUTO FOILED. (Box 1)
      CONTENTS: 38ABC
      LRC #: SS 5
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1975-09-09; TR-14107; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, MONO, HALF TRACK, ONE SIDE, dubbing master, edited, foiled auto. (Box 1)
      Contents: 63ABC, 64ABC,65AB,66AB
      LRC #: SS 6
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1975-09-22; TR-14108; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, mono, edited, one side, half track. Foiled auto (Box 1)
      Contents: 89B, 91ABC, 92B, 93AB, 94A
      LRC #: SS 7
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1977-06-13; TR-14109; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, mono, duplicate copy, half track, foiled auto. (Box 1)
      Contents: 40ABC, 41AB, 42AB
      LRC #: SS 8
    - Oral Spanish Review, 1977-06-13; TR-14110; Dalbor; Sturcken; 7.5 IPS, MONO, MASTER, HALF TRACK. (Box 1)
      CONTENTS:43AB, 44A, 45A, LAB TEST VII ABC`
      LRC #: SS 9
    - Beginning College German. A Comprehensive Approach, 1980-08-16; TR-14111; Haas, W.; Mathieu, G.B.; John Wiley and Sons; track a, 3.75 speed, head tail foil, c-45, duplicate (Box 2)
      contents: chapter 4, part 2
      LRC #: GCA 10.1
    - Beginning College German. A Comprehensive Approach, 1980-08-16; TR-14112; Haas, W.; Mathieu, G.B.; John Wiley and Sons; track a, 3.75 speed, head tail foil, c-90, duplicate (Box 2)
      contents: chapter 10 excersise 8
      LRC #: GCA 12,2
    - Beginning College German. A Comprehensive Approach, 1980-08-16; TR-14113; Haas, W.; Mathieu, G.B.; John Wiley and Sons; track a, 3.75 speed, head tail foil, duplicate (Box 2)
      contents: chapter 12 exercise 10-end
      LRC #: GCA 4.3
    - German Supplementary Lab Exercises, German 121 and 122, 1983-11; TR-14114; Valk, G.; Lohnes and Stotman; 7.5, original recording, head tail foil, track a. (Box 2)
      contents: assignments 1,2 (supp lab exercises for Ger 121/122)
      LRC #: GLS 1
    - German Supplementary Lab Exercises, German 121 and 123, 1983-04; TR-14115; Valk, G.; Lohnes and Stotman; 7.5, original recording, head tail foil, track a. (Box 2)
      contents: conversation (supp tape for ger 1221/122)
      LRC #: GLS 2
    - German Supplementary Lab Exercises, German 121 and 124, 1983-04; TR-14116; Valk, G.; Lohnes and Stotman; 7.5, original recording, head tail foil, track a. (Box 2)
      contents: Deutsch Witze (Ger 121/122 supp)
      LRC #: GLS 3
    - German Supplementary Lab Exercises, German 121 and 125, 1983-04-13; TR-14117; Valk, G.; Lohnes and Stotman; 7.5, original recording, head tail foil, track a. (Box 2)
      contents: supp tape 4 w/ song
      LRC #: GLS 4
    - Rehder and Twaddell: German, 1958, 1958; TR-14118; Rehder; Twaddell; Henry Holt and Co; single track 7.5 IPS (Box 2)
      reel 14 (page 277-300)
      LRC #: GW 14
    - Rehder and Twaddell: German, 1959, 1958; TR-14119; Rehder; Twaddell; Henry Holt and Co; single track 7.5 IPS (Box 2)
      reel 15 (page 300-312)
      LRC #: GW 15
    - Rehder and Twaddell: German, 1960, 1958; TR-14120; Rehder; Twaddell; Henry Holt and Co; single track 7.5 IPS (Box 2)
      reel 16 (page 313-330)
      LRC #: GW 16
    - Rehder and Twaddell: German, 1961, 1958; TR-14121; Rehder; Twaddell; Henry Holt and Co; single track 7.5 IPS (Box 2)
      reel 17 (page 330-343)
      LRC #: GW 17
    - Rehder and Twaddell: German, 1962, 1958; TR-14122; Rehder; Twaddell; Henry Holt and Co; single track 7.5 IPS (Box 2)
      reel 18( page 343-366)
      LRC #: GW 18
    - Rehder and Twaddell: German, 1963, 1958; TR-14123; Rehder; Twaddell; Henry Holt and Co; single track 7.5 IPS (Box 2)
      reel 19 ( page 366-384)
      LRC #: GW 19
    - Rehder and Twaddell: German, 1964, 1958; TR-14124; Rehder; Twaddell; Henry Holt and Co; single track 7.5 IPS (Box 2)
      reel 20 ( page 384-400)
      LRC #: GW 20
    - Rehder and Twaddell: German, 1965, 1958; TR-14125; Rehder; Twaddell; Henry Holt and Co; single track 7.5 IPS (Box 2)
      reel 21 (page 400-413)
      LRC #: GW 21
    - Rehder and Twaddell: German, 1966, 1958; TR-14126; Rehder; Twaddell; Henry Holt and Co; single track 7.5 IPS (Box 2)
      reel 22 (page 414-427)
      LRC #: GW 22
    - BRL German B, Undated; TR-14127; 3.75 IPS (Box 2)
      Rell 13. COULD NOT GET TO PLAY
      LRC #: GB 13
    - Spanish Reading Dialogues, Undated; TR-14128 (Box 7)
      LRC #: SDL 1
    - Spanish Reading Dialogues, Undated; TR-14129 (Box 7)
      LRC #: SDL 10
    - Spanish Reading Dialogues, Undated; TR-14130 (Box 7)
      LRC #: SDL 11
    - Spanish Reading Dialogues, Undated; TR-14131 (Box 7)
      LRC #: SDL 12